<resources>
    <string name="app_name">LEADPREPPER</string>
    <string name="lead_button_text">Lead Manual</string>
    <string name="warrior_button_text">Warrior Knowledge Quizzes</string>
    <string name="command_button_text">USAF Chain Of Command</string>
    <string name="majcom_button_text">USAF Major Commands</string>
    <string name="mission_button_text">Mission Statements</string>
    <string name="code_button_text">Code Of Conduct</string>
    <string name="qoutes_button_text">Quotes</string>
    <string name="song_button_text">AirForce Song</string>
    <string name="creed_button_text">Airmen\'s Creed</string>
    <string name="myQuiz_button_text">MyQuizes</string>
    <string name="prompt_text">Please choose a quiz</string>

    <string-array
        name="chain_of_command_quiz">
        <item>Who is the President of the United States?</item>
        <item>The Honourable Donald J Trump</item>
        <item>Who is the Secretary of Defense?</item>
        <item>The Honourable James N. Mattis</item>
        <item>Who is the Secretary of the Air Force?</item>
        <item>The Honourable Lisa Disbrow</item>
        <item>Who is the USAF Chief of staff?</item>
        <item>General David L. Goldfein</item>
        <item>Who is the Air Education and Training Command commander?</item>
        <item>Lt General Darryl L. Roberson</item>
        <item>Who is the Air University commander?</item>
        <item>Lt General Steven L. Kwast</item>
        <item>Who is the Holm Center Commander?</item>
        <item>Brigadier General Steven D. Garland</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array
        name="majcom_quiz">
        <item>Where is Air Mobility Command?</item>
        <item>Scott AFB, IL</item>
        <item>Where is Air Combat Command?</item>
        <item>Joint Base Langley-Eustis, VA</item>
        <item>Where is Air Education and Training Command?</item>
        <item>Joint Base San Antonio-Randolph, TX</item>
        <item>Where is Air Force Space Command?</item>
        <item>Peterson AFB, CO</item>
        <item>Where is Air Force Special Operations Command?</item>
        <item>Hulburt Field, FL</item>
        <item>Where is United States Air Forces in Europe?</item>
        <item>Ramstein AB, Germany</item>
        <item>Where is Pacific Air Forces?</item>
        <item>Joint Base Pearl Harbor-Hickam, HI</item>
        <item>Where is Air Force Material Command?</item>
        <item>Wright-Patterson AFB, OH</item>
        <item>Where is Air Force Reserve Command?</item>
        <item>Robins AFB, GA</item>
        <item>Where is Air Force Global Strike Command?</item>
        <item>Barkdale AFB, LA</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="mission">
        <item>What is the Air Force Mission?</item>
        <item>To Fly, Fight and Win... In Air, Space, and CyberSpace</item>
        <item>What is the Hold Center Mission?</item>
        <item>Develop the Best Air Force Leaders and Citizens of Character, Dedicated to Serving the Nation</item>
        <item>What is the AFROTC Mission?</item>
        <item>Develop Premier Leaders of Character for Tomorrow\'s Air Force</item>
        <item>What is the AFROTC LEAD Mission?</item>
        <item>Train and Evaluate Cadets for Potential Entry int othe Professinal Officer Course</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="code">
        <item>What is the first article of the Code of Conduct?</item>
        <item>I am an American, fighting in the forces which guard my country and our way of life.
            I am prepared to give my life in their defense. </item>
        <item>What is the second article of the Code of Conduct?</item>
        <item>I will never surrender of my own free will. If in command,
            I will never surrender the members of my command while they still have the means to resist. </item>
        <item>What is the third article of the Code of Conduct?</item>
        <item>If I am captured, I will continue to resist by all means available.
            I will make every effort to escape and aid others to escape.
            I will accept neither parole nor special favors from the enemy. </item>
        <item>What is the fourth article of the Code of Conduct></item>
        <item>If I become a prisoner of war, I will keep faith with my fellow prisoners.
            I will give no information nor take part in any action which might be harmful to my comrades.
            If I am senior I will take command.
            If not I will obey the lawful orders of those appointed over me and back them up in every way. </item>
        <item>What is the fifth article of the Code of Conduct?</item>
        <item>When questioned, should I become a prisoner of war, I am required to give name, rank, service number, and date of birth.
            I will evade answering further questions to the utmost of my ability.
            I will make no oral or written statements disloyal to my country and its allies or harmful to their cause.</item>
        <item>What is the sixth article of the Code of Conduct?</item>
        <item>I will never forget that I am an American, fighting for freedom, responsible for my actions,
            and dedicated to the principles which made my country free.
            I will trust in my God and in the United States of America. </item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="Quotes">
        <item>What is the quote by General Robert E. Lee?</item>
        <item>“Duty then is the sublimest word in the English language.
            You should do your duty in all things.  You can never do more.
            You should never wish to do less.” </item>
        <item>What is the quote by General Joseph L. Collins?</item>
        <item>“The American people rightly look to their military leaders to be not only skilled
             in the technical aspects of the profession of arms, but to be men of integrity.”</item>
        <item>What is the quote by General Omar Bradley?</item>
        <item>“Leadership is intangible; therefore no weapon ever designed can replace it.” </item>
        <item>What is the quote by General Nathan Twining?</item>
        <item>“If our air forces are never used, they have achieved their finest goal.”</item>
        <item>What is the quote by General Dwight D. Eisenhower?</item>
        <item>“If I didn’t have air supremacy, I wouldn’t be here.” </item>
        <item>What is the quote by General Curtis E. Lemay?</item>
        <item>“I don’t mind being called tough, because in this racket, it’s tough guys who lead the survivors.”</item>
        <item>What is the quote by General Ulysses S. Grant?</item>
        <item>“In every battle, there comes a time when both sides consider themselves beaten; then he who continues the attack wins.”</item>
        <item>What is the quote by John Stuart Mill?</item>
        <item>“War is an ugly thing, but not the ugliest of things.  The decayed and degraded state of moral and patriotic feeling,
            which thinks that nothing is worth war, is much worse.  The person, who has nothing for which he
            is willing to fight, nothing which is more important than his own personal safety,
            is a miserable creature and has no chance of being free unless made and kept so by the exertions of better men than himself.” </item>
        <item>What is the quote by General Charles A. Gaberiel?</item>
        <item>“Integrity is the fundamental premise for military service in a free society.
            Without integrity, the moral pillars of our military strength, public trust, and self-respect are lost.” </item>
        <item>What is the quote by Father Denis Edward O\'Brien?</item>
        <item>“It is the soldier, not the reporter, who has given us the freedom of the press.
            It is the soldier, not the poet,who has given us the freedom of speech.
            It is the soldier, not the campus organizer, who has given us the freedom todemonstrate.
            It is the soldier who salutes the flag,
            who serves beneath the flag, and whose coffin is draped by the flag, who allows the protestor to burn the flag.”</item>
        <item>What is the quote by Alfred Thayer Mahan?</item>
        <item>“War, once declared, must be waged offensively, aggressively.  The enemy must not be fended off; but smitten down.
            You may then spare him every exaction, relinquish every gain, but ‘til then he must be struck incessantly and remorselessly.” </item>
        <item>What is the quote by General George S. Patton?</item>
        <item>“There is only one sort of discipline – PERFECT DISCIPLINE.
            Men cannot have good battle discipline and poor administrative discipline.”</item>
        <item>What is the quote by General Daniel S. "Chappie" James?</item>
        <item>“The power of excellence is overwhelming.  It is always in demand, and nobody cares about its color.” </item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="afSong">
        <item>What is the first verse of the Air Force Song?</item>
        <item>Off we go into the wild blue yonder,
            Climbing high into the sun;
            Here they come zooming to meet our thunder,
            At ‘em boys, give‘er the gun!
            Down we dive, spouting our flame from under,
            Off with one helluva roar;
            We live in fame or go down in flame. Hey!
            Nothing’ll stop the U.S. Air Force!</item>
        <item>What is the second verse of the Air Force Song?</item>
        <item>Minds of men fashioned a crate of thunder,
            Sent it high into the blue;
            Hands of men blasted the world asunder;
            How they lived God only knew!
            Souls of men dreaming of skies to conquer
            Gave us wings, ever to soar!
            With scouts before and bombers galore. Hey!
            Nothing’ll stop the U.S. Air Force! </item>
        <item>What is the third verse of the Air Force Song?</item>
        <item>Here’s a toast to the host
            Of those who love the vastness of the sky,
            To a friend we send a message of his brother men who fly.
            We drink to those who gave their all of old,
            Then down we roar to score the rainbow’s pot of gold.
            A toast to the host of men we boast, the U.S. Air Force!</item>
        <item>What is the fourth verse of the Air Force Song?</item>
        <item>Off we go into the wild sky yonder,  Keep the wings level and true;
            If you’d live to be a gray-haired wonder  Keep the nose out of the blue!
            Flying men, guarding the nation’s border,  We’ll be there, followed by more!
            In echelon we carry on.  Hey!
            Nothing’ll stop the U.S. Air Force!</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="airmen_creed">
        <item>What is the first stanza of the Airmen\'s Creed?</item>
        <item>I AM AN AMERICAN AIRMAN.
            I AM A WARRIOR
            I HAVE ANSWERED MY NATION’S CALL.</item>
        <item>What is the second stanza of the Airmen\'s Creed?</item>
        <item>I AM AN AMERICAN AIRMAN.
            MY MISSION IS TO FLY, FIGHT AND WIN.
            I AM FAITHFUL TO A PROUD HERITAGE,
            A TRADITION OF HONOR,
            AND A LEGACY OF VALOR.</item>
        <item>What is the third stanza of the Airmen\'s Creed?</item>
        <item>I AM AN AMERICAN AIRMAN,
            GUARDIAN OF FREEDOM AND JUSTICE,
            MY NATION’S SWORD AND SHIELD,
            ITS SENTRY AND AVENGER.
            I DEFEND MY COUNTRY WITH MY LIFE.</item>
        <item>What is the fourth stanza of the Airmen\'s Creed?</item>
        <item>I AM AN AMERICAN AIRMAN:
            WINGMAN, LEADER, WARRIOR.
            I WILL NEVER LEAVE AN AIRMAN BEHIND,
            I WILL NEVER FALTER,
            AND I WILL NOT FAIL.</item>
    </string-array>

</resources>
